<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="heading">Digital Image Processing</string>
    <string name="subheading">Acknowledgments</string>
    <string name="article"><b>We are indebted to a number of individuals</b> in academic circles, industry, and gov
ernment who have contributed to this edition of the book. In particular, we wish
to extend our appreciation to Hairong Qi and her students, Zhifei Zhang and
Chengcheng Li, for their valuable review of the material on neural networks, and for
their help in generating examples for that material.
We also want to thank Ernesto
Bribiesca Correa for providing and reviewing material on slope chain codes, and
Dirk Padfield for his many suggestions and review of several chapters in the book.
We appreciate Michel Kocher’s many thoughtful comments and suggestions over
the years on how to improve the book. Thanks also to Steve Eddins for his sugges
tions on MATLAB and related software issues.
<b><i>Numerous individuals have contributed to material carried</i></b> over from the previ
ous to the current edition of the book. Their contributions have been important in so
many different ways that we find it difficult to acknowledge them in any other way
but alphabetically. We thank Mongi A. Abidi, Yongmin Kim, Bryan Morse, Andrew
Oldroyd, Ali M. Reza, Edgardo Felipe Riveron, Jose Ruiz Shulcloper, and Cameron
H.G. Wright for their many suggestions on how to improve the presentation and/or
the scope of coverage in the book. We are also indebted to Naomi Fernandes at the
MathWorks for providing us with MATLAB software and support that were impor
tant in our ability to create many of the examples and experimental results included
in this edition of the book.
         www.ImageProcessingPlace.com
 A significant percentage of the new images used in this edition (and in some
cases their history and interpretation) were obtained through the efforts of indi
viduals whose contributions are sincerely appreciated. In particular, we wish to
acknowledge the efforts of Serge Beucher, Uwe Boos, Michael E. Casey, Michael
W. Davidson, Susan L. Forsburg, Thomas R. Gest, Daniel A. Hammer, Zhong He,
Roger Heady, Juan A. Herrera, John M. Hudak, Michael Hurwitz, Chris J. Johannsen,
Rhonda Knighton, Don P. Mitchell, A. Morris, Curtis C. Ober, David. R. Pickens,
Michael Robinson, Michael Shaffer, Pete Sites, Sally Stowe, Craig Watson, David
K. Wehe, and Robert A. West. We also wish to acknowledge other individuals and
organizations cited in the captions of numerous figures throughout the book for
their permission to use that material.
We also thank Scott Disanno, Michelle Bayman, Rose Kernan, and Julie Bai for
their support and significant patience during the production of the book.</string>
</resources>